### JEAN PIERRE MUGABO

# 3D Designer & Graphic Designer

+91 866 0141 359



petermugabo22@gmail.com



NH 207 Bengaluru, Karnataka , India



#### **PROFILE**

I am a Rwandan by Birth. I am a passionate 3d Designer and graphic designer. I have all the required competitive experience I got from the international Fabrication Lab of Rwanda [FABLAB Rwanda]. additionally, I am Industrious and ingenious.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Graphic Designer
At GITAM STUDENT LIFE

#### **April 2022 - Present**

Working as a Graphic Designer, Event organizer, Making posters and banners, Logo Designer, and Poster verification before publication. Event Branding activities and Video Editing.

# CNC Machinist And 3D Designer At FABLAB RWANDA

#### November, 2018 - February 2020

Working as a 3D Designer, CNC shoot boot, and Laser Cutter Operator.

Interior Designer and decorator.

## Automobile Workshop Instructor At C.F.PRO.RU TVET SCHOOL

#### **April, 2017 - November, 2018**

Supervising all Workshop activities and store keeping.

#### **EDUCATION**

### Bachelor Of Technology In MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

#### GITAM University | 2020 - Present

- Undergraduate degree in Mechanical Engineering.
- Mechanical product Design Project Research.

## Advanced Diploma In MOTOR VEHICLE MECHANICS

#### Rwanda Polythechnic | 2014 - 2016

 Advanced Diploma In Motor vehicle Mechanics [Grade 48/60]

#### **SKILL**

- 3D Modeling & Design
- Photo Editing
- Video Editing
- Public Speaking
- Front End Web Design
- 3D Printing



#### SOFTWARE AND P-LANGUAGE

- SOLID WORK
- ADOBE Illustrator, Photoshop & Premiere Pro
- Auto CAD
- Sketch UP
- Python, HTML, CSS & React Js